Previously on JoJo's Bizarre Adventure!
That's her!
That woman there is the stand user!
I do appreciate your forwardness, but
you need to work on your approach,
you naughty naughty man!
Oh my god!
I forgot to tell you, whatever you do,
it's imperative that you refrain
from touching any electrical outlets!
I'm afraid I already did, Mr. Joestar!
But if what I know about magnets is
true, we're being forced together.
Mr.
Joestar, I really hate saying this, but...
Yeah, I know, we've gotten
ourselves into a world of trouble.
Let's
go.
In the last page of the last page,
End of the world!
Hora!
Hey, wait a sec! Damn it all!
Look!
She's getting away after her!
Blasted!
Now my body's a magnet!
I can't believe we allowed ourselves
to play right into her hands!
Calm down, Avdol!
You getting hysterical
isn't helping anything!
Focus on figuring out how to
overpower this blasted stand. Damn it!
Now where did that woman run off to?
I don't care. Anywhere.
Well, we can't keep rolling
in the dirt forever.
Why don't we try slowly standing up?
Give it a go.
All right, we did it.
Now that we're upright, the next step
is to try pulling away from each other.
However,
I think it's going to be
easier said than done,
since the magnetic force that's currently
holding us together has been doubled.
But for now, let's use that fence to
try getting out of this predicament.
We can do it, Abtol!
Get those stomach muscles ready
and make sure you stay in sync!
Ready when you are, Mr.
Joestar!
Mr.
Joestar, this is one of the most
embarrassing things I've ever done!
What do you think you're looking at?
Can't you see that we're just
practicing our dance moves? True!
What a perfect day for dancing outdoors!
Now run along!
Get out of here, dammit!
There we go!
Almost got it, Abdaal!
And one!
And two!
We did it!
We made it and we're still standing!
Yes, a remarkable feat!
Abdaal, now that we've gotten over
here, do you think you can slide off me?
I think I might be able to. All right.
Here's what we're going to
do, so listen carefully.
I'll hang on to the fence as tightly
as I can while you slide down.
Free yourself once you've
gotten to the tip of my foot.
Do you see how our faces are stuck together
as opposed to the other way around?
Well,
it's more than likely a sign that my feet
and your head should repel each other.
Yes, that makes a lot of sense.
That's the way, Abdal.
Just keep moving.
Uh, hey, what's the
matter with you, Avdol?
Don't you think this
position is a little...
This pose is highly suggestive, Mr.
Toastar.
If anyone were to see us, they
would be inclined to think that...
Don't come off it!
No one's looking at us!
Hurry up and slide off my...
Those little brats came back
and brought their friends!
Why don't you take a hike?
There's nothing to see, so knock
it off with a staring, would ya?
I said beat it, you little ankle biters!
Get out of here!
Take off!
I have to hurry up and get off
me before this gets any worse!
I'm trying as hard as I can!
I can't believe this is happening to me!
The embarrassment!
Alright, I'll be the one to move! Mr.
Joestar, please slow down!
Oh! Oh!
Mr.
Joestar, moving around like that
makes it seem as though we're...
Oh no, it's that old hag again!
I come back expecting
to find my handsome man,
and instead my eyes are
assaulted with this?
How dare you tie with the
fragile gift of a maiden's heart!
You filthy cheater!
For the love of God, hurry, Abdel!
She's getting closer and I can
already feel the tears coming!
There they are, Father Skel-Draw!
Help me!
Oh, my God!
Oh, little dog, you've got it all wrong!
We did it!
We need to stay far apart from each other!
Your magnetic pull is getting
more powerful by the second!
It serves you great, you dead pull!
You and your boy toy go to hell!
What the...
There she is!
We found her!
Just look at her having
her morning cigarette!
Avdol, try going after her from that side.
We can't let her get
away from us this time.
She's cunning, so this may be a trap.
This can't be! Hey, Mr.
Joestar, it would appear as though we've
already fallen right into her trap.
Huh?
They're railroad tracks!
I don't think we're going to
be able to get off that easily.
Are you kidding me?
It would seem that we're
stuck together again!
Son of a bitch!
Mr.
Joestar, something is coming!
That sound!
Oh no, we have to get the hell
out of here as fast as we can!
Avdol, I need you to use Magician's
Red to burn through the tracks!
We need to get out of here!
But Mr.
Joestar, I don't think that would be...
It's here! There's a train!
Hurry up and melt those tracks!
I tried telling you, Mr.
Joestar!
If I were to burn away these tracks...
The train would derail, and innocent
people would go tumbling to their deaths!
Shit!
That damn woman is pure,
unadulterated evil!
I'm almost positive my vines would be
able to hold her, but at that distance,
she's too far out of range
for them to even reach her!
So our best bet is me
trying to pull us free
from the tracks using
that post as an anchor!
It's no use!
The magnetic pull is even
stronger than it was before!
Mr.
Joestar, it's life or death!
You can't stop pulling no matter what!
It's coming!
You have to pull harder!
That didn't work!
I win.
I took care of them for you, Lord Dio.
Now that that's done, I'm going to
do away with Jotaro and Polnare.
Good thinking, Avdol.
Only someone as clever
as you would burn the
railroad tracks and dig
a trench underneath.
You see, Mr.
Joestar, unlike that earlier incident,
Muhammad Avdol does indeed
have a decent modicum of class.
Doing things this way is
a little more my style.
So you think you've outsmarted me?
You...
obnoxious pieces of shit!
Elections, run!
Me too, Hermit Purple!
Now we've got you.
Unfortunately for you, young lady?
I've got to keep a grip on
your neck until you pass out!
so you can count on being in the
hospital for at least a week or so.
I can't just let you and your
magnetic power run free, can I?
Oh, your imagination's running wild.
Sorry to disappoint, boys, but
my breasts aren't getting larger.
But there's no need to worry yourselves
because your magnetism's
growing even stronger.
And lucky for me, I just happened
to stuff my bra with weapons!
Mr.
Shuichi, we have incoming!
But you should run!
Your magnetism will keep intensifying.
Well, at least until your bodies
are crushed to tiny pieces. Ugh!
She's getting away again!
No, I don't think so.
It's all part of her strategy.
She's moving farther away from us in
order to maintain a safe distance.
Remember, that woman's a stand user, so
she needs to stay close to her target.
If she gets too close to us,
we'll be able to catch her.
But if she's too far out of
range, her power won't work.
This magnetism is still just a stand.
The normal rules apply,
which means if she puts too much distance
between us, the magnetism should weaken.
So what should we do?
If we don't get free, the magnetic
force will just continue to intensify.
Should we keep running
until we're out of range?
That might be our best bet. No way.
We might be able to get away from our
powers for a short amount of time,
but the stand would still prevail.
I've run away from fights before,
but I've only done so when running
was part of the overall strategy.
No matter how hopeless things look,
Joseph Joestar never throws in the towel.
The real showdown begins now!
I've drawn a map of the town.
Here's our current position.
And here's where the woman's going.
As long as she continues
moving down this road,
she'll eventually loop around
and head back this way.
We'll split up and...
Right here is where
we'll catch that witch.
It doesn't matter if she's a woman or not.
When we catch her, she's
getting a taste of my bones!
Let's get going!
Check it out! Oh, yeah.
Someone's cut the rails.
Good.
The locals are here.
I'm sure one of them will have
the foresight to notify the
authorities about the tracks
before the next train arrives.
Come on!
Huh?
Something is definitely up. Hey!
Did you hear someone cut the rail line?
What about all the trains?
Luckily, they've stopped running.
At least for now.
Someone actually cut the rail line?
People nowadays sure are
sick, don't you think?
Who in their right mind would do
something so terrible, Major Douche Canoe?
Oh, Jotaro, you want to know what I think?
Rotten people always get
what's coming to them.
You mark my words, they'll get theirs.
I saved three months' salary all for this.
Will you marry me? Oh, no!
Huh? What the? Wait!
Wait at the... The ring!
Those morons are getting closer to me.
But at this rate, they'll never catch me.
Huh?
Almost there.
I must say, you're looking
a little weighted down.
But don't worry, the wild
goose chase ends here.
Interestingly enough,
it would seem that the two of us are more
familiar with this town than you are.
You should take a look behind you.
You're now caught between us, and
there's nowhere for you to run.
It may have taken a while to get
here, but the tables have turned.
So you think I have nowhere to go?
You boys truly haven't
realized it yet, have you?
You only thought you were hunting me when
really I was luring you
here the entire time.
Look up, idiots!
High voltage power lines! Oh no!
The power lines are...
That's right!
Power lines are extremely magnetic!
I'm afraid you're going
to fry this time, Joestar!
But you should sweat!
Yeah!
Hermit purple!
Avdol might be able to defend
himself for now with his flames.
But not you.
Time to die, Joestar. My stand,
the goddess Bast, is the perfect trap,
and it's also far more powerful
than your hermit purple!
Hope you've said your prayers,
because it's time to die!
Vile woman, my flames will
burn you and your evil alive!
My entire body is being pulled
in another direction! I...
I can't resist!
My flame should be strong enough to
melt the steel without a problem.
But I can't defend
myself from every attack.
This weight is crushing me.
I can't hold it any longer.
Joseph Joestar,
since you're going to die anyway, I can
confess that I find you to be quite a catch.
It's true that I only
knew you for a short time,
but you were so clever and hilarious.
Not to mention your experience would
make younger men green with envy.
Plus, you're very handsome.
I know that you and I are decades apart,
but if I'm being honest with myself,
you would have made a splendid lover.
Well, if that's how you
truly feel about me,
then what do you say you give me a hand?
I've seen the light and
realized that your stand is
way more powerful than
mine could ever hope to be!
I can't hold it anymore!
Please, I'm begging you!
You have to turn off the magnetism!
Well, I suppose I could.
But no, I don't think I will.
While you are exceptionally handsome,
you're nowhere near as
good-looking as Lord Dio.
So, you're saying that you refuse to
turn off the power no matter what?
Exactly right.
Now, don't you have some dying to do?
Even though I'm grambling to you?
I won't say it again, you idiot.
If that's how you're going to be,
then it's your loss, young lady.
What?!
Shit! Shit!
Weren't you listening to us earlier or
you've been caught between us the whole time?
Magnets are attracted
to each other, you know?
It's too late to do anything about it now,
but getting between us
was your biggest blunder.
There's no way she can hear you, Mr.
Joestar.
She's already lost consciousness.
All the metal and magnetic
forces crushed her,
and it's very likely that she's broken
more than a few bones in the process.
All right, why don't we get that
breakfast we were talking about?
Yes, a wonderful idea.
All this running around
has made me rather hungry.
Is it really only 9 a .m.? Damn... you...
pieces of shit!
Those two are taking forever!
As long as they've been in there,
you'd think they were putting on
makeup and dressing for a gala.
And it's almost 9 a .m.
They may have run into
an enemy on the way here.
You think we should see where
they ran off to? I guess.
Good grief.
It's time to go, Iggy.
Yeah, yeah, I know you're hungry.
You're not the only one.
Believe me.
Joseph and Avdol are in the middle
of doing battle with Mariah.
So I, Alessi, shall take on the great
honor of killing Jotaro and Polnareff.
Thank you.
All right, we're going to take a bath, so
let's take those clothes off, shall we?
Attaboy.
I'll take them off for you.
I'll clean those wounds.
Attaboy.
Are you positive it's okay
for me to touch you like this?
Attaboy.
You